[
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/5 * 9/5?",
    "choice1": "4/10",
    "choice2": "36/25",
    "choice3": "7/9",
    "choice4": "1 entero",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/3 * 1/3?",
    "choice1": "4/9",
    "choice2": "4/5",
    "choice3": "3/7",
    "choice4": "10/6",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 2/7 ÷ 1/7?",
    "choice1": "3/3",
    "choice2": "14/7",
    "choice3": "4/8",
    "choice4": "4/5",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/5 ÷ 1/5?",
    "choice1": "2/5",
    "choice2": "3/7",
    "choice3": "20/5",
    "choice4": "5/5",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿A cuanto equivale 1/2 * 3/5?",
    "choice1": "1 entero 4/5",
    "choice2": "3/10",
    "choice3": "6/5",
    "choice4": "4/20",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 5/3 * 2/2?",
    "choice1": "7/3",
    "choice2": "8/2",
    "choice3": "5/4",
    "choice4": "10/6",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿A cuanto equivale 8/4 ÷ 3/2?",
    "choice1": "4/5",
    "choice2": "20/8",
    "choice3": "12/4",
    "choice4": "5/4",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 1/5 ÷ 2/10?",
    "choice1": "4/5",
    "choice2": "1 entero",
    "choice3": "7/5",
    "choice4": "8/10",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/4 * 5/6?",
    "choice1": "10/4",
    "choice2": "1/6",
    "choice3": "1 entero 1/4",
    "choice4": "20/24",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿A cuanto equivale 9/7 * 4/14?",
    "choice1": "2/6",
    "choice2": "15/14",
    "choice3": "36/98",
    "choice4": "10/9",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
